(乘务员专用 非紧急出口)
(伦敦西区公演)
(地铁　公共地下铁路)
谢谢
Thank you.
还要点别的吗
Would you like something else?
不  不了  暂时不用  我在等…
No. No, no, not just yet. I'm waiting...
我在等一个人
I'm expecting someone.
你是不是经常来光顾这家店
Would this be one of your regular haunts?
其实也并没有经常来
I don't have any regular haunts.
给我看看
Let me see it.
有时我好像还觉得它依然挂在脖子上
Sometimes I imagine I still feel it around my neck.
毕竟我戴了它这么多年
I carried it for so many years.
你戴着感觉如何
How does it feel around yours?
我们可以解除它的束缚
We can free each other of it.
我们的麻瓜朋友们是不是很聒噪
Love to chatter, don't they, our Muggle friends.
但是必须承认  他们泡的茶确实不错
Though one must admit, they make a good cup of tea.
你的所作所为太过疯狂
What you're doing is madness.
我们约定过要一起做
It's what we said we'd do.
当时太年轻
I was young.
- 我还…  - 还对我承诺过
- I was...  - Committed. To me.
关于我们
To us.
不
No.
我曾与你同道是因为
I went along because...
因为什么
Because?
因为我爱上了你
Because I was in love with you.
是啊
Yes.
但是原因并非如此
But that's not why you went along.
你说过我们要一起重塑这个世界
It was you who said we could reshape the world.
你说那是我们的权利
That it was our birthright.
你闻得到吗
Can you smell it?
一股恶臭
The stench.
你当真打算背叛自己的同类吗
Do you really intend to turn your back on your own kind?
为了这些畜生
For these animals?
有没有你  我都将焚毁他们的世界  阿不思
With or without you, I'll burn down their world, Albus.
无论你做什么都无法阻止我
There's nothing you can do to stop me.
好好喝茶吧
Enjoy your cup of tea.
它快生了
She's ready.
太美了
Beautiful.
好了  你们两个
All right, you two.
接下来  可能有点麻烦
Now, the tricky bit.
(皇家辰星汽轮公司 纽约)
箱子飞来
Accio.
真的对不起
I'm so sorry.
双胞胎
Twins.
你生了双胞胎
You had twins.
《神奇动物3：邓布利多之谜》
都回避
Leave us.
拿出来
Show me.
他们都说这个东西很特别
The others, they said it was special.
它可是意义非凡
Ooh, it's beyond special.
你看
See?
看到它眼睛了吗
See its eyes?
它的双眼能看透一切
Those eyes see everything.
每当麒麟诞生之时
When a Qilin is born,
能给世界带来变革的领袖  也会随之崛起
a righteous leader will rise to change our world forever.
它的出生将带来改变  克雷登斯
Her birth brings change, Credence,
改变一切
to everything.
干得漂亮
You did well.
去吧  休息一下
Go. Rest.
好了
There.
(悬赏5000  通缉令  格林德沃)
看来你不打算告诉我  这是要去做什么  对吧
I don't suppose you'd like to tell me what this is about, would you?
他就说要见一见  还让我一定要带上你
He just asked that we meet, and that I be sure to bring you.
嗯  好吧
Hmm. Right.
(霍格沃茨)
我猜你们是来这里找我哥哥的
Here to meet my brother, I expect.
不  先生  我们来见阿不思·邓布利多
No, sir. We're here to see Albus Dumbledore.
他就是我哥哥
That would be my brother.
抱歉  我  太好了  我是纽特·斯卡曼德
Sorry. I'm, um... Brilliant. I'm Newt Scamander,
这位是忒修斯
and this is Theseus..
上二楼  左手第一个房间
Up the stairs. First on the left.
纽特说过为何而来吗
Has Newt told you why you're here?
他本该说
Was he meant to?
不
No.
其实就是这样的
As a matter of fact.
有件事情  我们
There's something that we, uh...
应该是邓布利多想和你谈一谈
That, uh, Dumbledore wishes to speak to you about.
这算是一个提议
It's a proposal.
好吧
All right.
你肯定知道这是什么
You know what this is, of course.
纽特在巴黎拿到的
Newt had it in Paris.
虽然不敢说我对这个东西有多么了解
I can't say I have much experience with such things,
但是它看上去是个血盟
but it looks to me to be a blood troth.
你说得没错
That would be correct.
这里面装的是谁的血
And whose blood is contained within?
我的  还有格林德沃的
Mine. And Grindelwald's.
- 这就是你不能对他出手的原因  - 是这样的
- I'm assuming that's why you can't move against him?  - Yes.
他对我也是如此
Nor he against me.
能问问你当初  为什么会做这样的事吗
Can I ask, what would possess you to make such a thing?
感情
Love.
傲慢自大  幼稚无知  怎么选都行
Arrogance. Naivete. Pick your poison.
我们当时都很年轻  一心想改变这个世界
We were young, we were going to transform the world.
就算有人变心
This ensured that we would,
血盟也能保证计划继续进行
even if one of us had a change of heart.
如果你要动手会有怎样的后果
And what would happen if you were to fight him?
不得不承认  这个东西真是太美了
It's really quite beautiful, you have to admit.
哪怕我仅仅产生一丝和他作对的念头
Were I to even think about defying it...
它都能感觉到  你们看
It knows, you see.
阿不思
Albus.
它能感应到我心中的背叛
It senses the betrayal in my heart.
阿不思
Albus.
这还算是最轻的后果
That would be the least of it.
虽是少年魔法  但如你们所见
Young man's magic, but as you can see,
威力十分强大
powerful magic.
根本无法可解
It can't be undone.
刚才说的提议  我想跟这麒麟有关是吗
So this proposal, I take it the Qilin has something to do with it?
他保证过不会说出去
He promises he won't tell a soul.
如果想要打败他  麒麟是计划的一部分
If we're to defeat him, the Qilin's only part of it.
我们熟悉的世界正走向毁灭
The world as we know it is coming undone.
盖勒特利用仇恨与偏执
Gellert's pulling it apart with hate,
将它分裂
bigotry.
在今天看似不可想象的事情
Things that seem unimaginable today will seem
有可能在明天将不可避免
inevitable tomorrow,
除非我们阻止他
if we don't stop him.
你若愿意按照我的吩咐去做
Should you agree to do what I ask,
就一定要相信我
you'll have to trust me.
即使本能告诉你不要这样做
Even when every instinct tells you not to.
说说看吧
Let's hear it.
是他派你来
Does he send you
监视我的吗
to spy on me?
不
No.
但是他会问起你
But he asks.
问你在想什么  情绪怎么样
What ya thinkin', what ya feeling.
那其他人呢
And the others?
他也问他们的想法和感受吗
Does he ask what they're thinking and feeling?
是的
Yes,
可是  主要问的是你
but it's mostly you.
你会告诉他吗
And do you tell him?
你会
You do.
现在是谁在读谁的想法呢
Who's reading whose mind now?
说说你看到的
Tell me what you see.
你姓邓布利多
You're a Dumbledore.
这是个很重要的家族
It's an important family.
这事你知道  因为他告诉过你
You know this because he's told you.
他也说过  是那家人抛弃了你
He's also told you they abandoned you.
你的存在
That you were a...
是个见不得人的秘密
A dirty secret.
他还说  邓布利多也抛弃了他
Um... He says Dumbledore abandoned him too,
他懂你的感受
and he knows how you feel.
正因为如此
And for that reason...
他才想让你亲手杀了他
For that reason, he's asked you to kill him.
请你离开这儿  奎妮
I want you to go now, Queenie.
我不会告诉他的
I don't tell him.
不是每次都说
Not always.
也没全说
Not everything.
(原谅我)
(请进 营业中)
嘿  我们打…
Hey, we're...
奎妮
Queenie.
嗨  亲爱的
Hi, sweetie.
亲爱的
Honey...
你看你的烘焙坊
look at your bakery.
现在变得空荡荡的
It's like a ghost town.
是啊  我太想你了
Yeah, well, I missed you.
哦  宝贝儿
Oh, baby.
快过来好吗
Why don't you come here?
快过来
Come here.
嘿  所有事情一定会好起来的
Hey. Everything's gonna be all right.
所有的事情都会一切正常的
Everything's gonna be just fine.
(科瓦尔斯基烘焙坊)
(不招工)
(里文顿大街)
嘿  美女
Hey, sweetheart,
怎么一个人来市里
what brings you downtown?
这么无聊的开场白
I really hope
真希望不是你想了一整天才憋出来的
you didn't spend all day coming up with that.
你想让我吓唬你  是这么想的吗
Oh, you want scary, is that what you want?
我想你其实也知道
You know what it is,
你就是没有吓人的气势
you just aren't menacing enough.
我觉得我气势还是挺吓人的
I think I'm plenty menacing.
我这样不吓人吗
Am I not menacing?
也许你要是同时挥动双臂
Maybe if you waved your arms around,
来点儿疯疯癫癫的感觉
you know, like a crazy man,
那样看起来会更吓人一些
then you'd appear more menacing.
就这样  再加把劲
That's good. A little more.
动作再大一点儿
A little more.
不要停  非常好
Keep going. Perfect.
三  二  一
Three, two, one.
别胡闹了  快离开这里
That's enough. Get outta here.
你想怎么样  烤面包的
What's on your mind, baker boy?
我的天哪  你们该为自己感到羞愧
Ah, jeez. You should be ashamed of yourselves.
我们没觉得
Oh, well, we're not.
她是个姑娘
It's a lady.
要不这样吧
I tell you what,
我让你先动手  来吧
I'll give you the first shot. Go ahead.
你确定  坏了
You sure? Oh, boy.
这是我最后一次给那个女人帮忙了  拉莉
Last time I ever help that woman out again. Lally!
对不起  弗兰克
Whoopsie, Frank.
只是我有时候控制不住力道
Sometimes I forget my own strength.
后面的事我自己来  真谢谢你们
I'll take it from here. Thank you!
不用客气
Welcome.
回头见  拉莉
Catch you later, Lally.
再见  斯坦利
Bye, Stanley.
有时间我会去你家一起玩巫师游戏
I'll be over for a game of Befudler Dudley soon.
没问题
All right.
那是我表哥斯坦利  他是个巫师
That's my cousin Stanley. He's a wizard.
不要
No.
求你了  一大早的  你就配合我一下
Please! It's early, don't make me work for it.
我说了我不想掺和进来
I said I wanted out, and I want out.
别这样  科瓦尔斯基先生
Come now, Mr. Kowalski.
我的心理医生还说世上根本没有巫师
Can't believe my therapist said you wizards don't exist.
那些钱都白花了
What a waste of money!
你知道我是个女巫  对吧
You do know I'm a witch, right?
对  听着
Yeah. Look...
你看起来像个好女巫
...you seem like a really nice witch.
你根本不知道我经历了什么
You don't know what I've been through with you people.
能不能求求你别再来打扰我了
So, could you please get out of my life?
- 大约是在一年多之前  - 我的天哪
- A little over a year ago...  - Oh, my...
为了申请一笔贷款用来做点儿小生意
...in the hopes of securing a small business loan,
你走进了斯蒂恩国家银行的大门
you walked through the doors of the Steen National Bank,
距离这儿大约有六个街区
located about six blocks from here.
你在那儿结识了纽特·斯卡曼德
You then made the acquaintance of Newt Scamander,
他是世上最杰出的
the world's foremost and,
也是独一无二的神奇动物学家
albeit only, magizoologist.
从此你认识了一个
You then learned of a world
自己之前从未察觉到的世界
you had previously been wholly unaware of.
你和女巫奎妮·戈德斯坦恩相识相爱
You met and fell in love with a witch named Queenie Goldstein,
而后被一忘皆空咒抹去了记忆
had your brain wiped by means of Obliviation,
但是咒法没有生效
only it didn't take.
于是后来  你和戈德斯坦恩小姐重逢
And as a result, you reunited with Ms. Goldstein who,
但是在你拒绝和她结婚之后
after your refusal to marry her, mm,
她毅然加入了
decided to join Gellert Grindelwald
盖勒特·格林德沃与他的邪恶大军
and his dark army of followers,
而且他们是四百多年来
who pose the single greatest threat
对你我两个世界和平最大的威胁
to both your world and ours in four centuries.
我说得怎么样
How did I do?
面面俱到
That was good.
除了奎妮变成坏人的那个部分
Except for the part about Queenie going over to the dark side.
我是说  对
I mean, yeah, she's
她确实古灵精怪
she's cuckoo.
但是她的心地比这岛上所有人都善良
But she's got a heart bigger than this whole crazy island,
而且她还特别聪明  你知道吗
and she's so smart, you know?
她能知道你脑子里在想些什么
She can legitimately read your brain, you know,
- 用你们的话…  - 叫摄神取念者
- she's a whatchamacallit...  - A Legilimens.
是的
Yeah.
听着
Look...
看见这个了吗
You see this?
看到这锅了吗
You see the pan?
我就好比这个平底锅
That's me, I'm the pan.
破旧不堪而且平平无奇  普通人一个
I'm all dented, dime-a-dozen. I'm just a schmo.
虽然我还不知道  你到底有什么疯狂的打算
I don't know what kind of crazy ideas you have in your head there,
女士  但是你肯定能找到  比我更合适的人
lady, but I'm sure as hell you could do a lot better than me.
再见
Goodbye.
我不这么认为  科瓦尔斯基先生
I don't think we can, Mr. Kowalski.
你明明可以躲在柜台后  可是你没有
You could have ducked under the counter, but you didn't.
你完全可以冷眼旁观  可是你也没有
You could have looked the other way, but you didn't.
事实就是  你情愿以身犯险
In fact, you were willing to put yourself in danger
也要去帮助一个完全陌生的人
to save a perfect stranger.
依我看
Seems to me
这个世界现在正需要  像你这样的普通人
you're just the kind of average Joe the world needs right now.
只是你自己还没发现
You just don't know it yet.
所以我来帮你看清楚
That's why I had to show you.
我们需要你  科瓦尔斯基先生
We need you, Mr. Kowalski.
好吧
All right.
叫雅各布就好
Call me Jacob.
我叫拉莉
Call me Lally.
拉莉
Lally.
我得把门锁好
I gotta lock up.
(抱歉 本店已打烊)
- 谢谢  - 这样好多了  雅各布
- Thanks.  - Much better, Jacob.
我想你知道这是怎么回事吧  雅各布
I believe you know how this works, Jacob.
(通缉令 悬赏: 5000)
(胜者将是谁 刘还是桑托斯)
魔法部那边是怎么说的  刘还是桑托斯
What did they say at the Ministry? Liu or Santos?
官方说法是魔法部保持中立
Officially, the Ministry takes no position.
可是私下里
Unofficially,
聪明人都押桑托斯赢
smart money's on Santos.
不过  换任何人都比沃格尔好
Although anyone would be better than Vogel.
任何人
Anyone?
选票上又没有他  卡玛
I don't believe he's on the ballot, Kama.
而且他还是一名逃犯
He also happens to be a fugitive.
这有什么区别
Is there a difference?
还在转  每次都天旋地转
Spinning! Always with the spinning.
雅各布  欢迎欢迎  我的好伙计
Jacob. Welcome. You brilliant man.
抱歉
Sorry.
当初我就知道  希克斯教授一定可以说动你
I was absolutely sure that Professor Hicks would convince you.
是啊  你是了解我的
Yeah. You know me, pal.
门钥匙这么好玩绝不能错过
I can't pass up a good Portkey.
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander.
希克斯教授  我们终于见面了
Professor Hicks. At long last.
那个  我和希克斯教授  多年来一直有书信往来
So, Professor Hicks and I, we've corresponded for many years,
可是一直未曾谋面
but we've never actually met.
她的高级魔咒学著作可是必读的作品
So, her book on advanced charm casting is a must-read.
纽特  你实在太客气了
Newt is far too kind.
《神奇动物》这本书
Fantastic Beasts
也是我布置给五年级学生的必读书籍
is required reading for all my fifth years.
现在  我来给大家介绍一下
Now, let me make some introductions.
这位是  邦缇·布罗德克
So, this is, um, Bunty Broadacre,
是我这七年来不可或缺的好助手
my indispensable assistant for the past seven years.
其实是八年
Eight... years.
又过了一百六十四天了
And 164 days.
看见了吧  她不可或缺
As you can see, indispensable.
- 这一位他是…  - 尤瑟夫·卡玛  幸会
- And this is...  - Yusuf Kama. Pleasure.
而且毫无疑问  你已经见过雅各布了
And you, obviously, already made Jacob's acquaintance.
纽特
Newt.
对了  这是我哥哥忒修斯
So... So, this is my brother, Theseus,
现在他在魔法部工作
and, um, he works for the Ministry.
其实我是英国傲罗办公室的负责人
Actually, head of the British Auror Office.
那我可得查查  确保我的魔杖注册没过期
Well, I'll have to ensure my wand registration's up to date.
是的
Yes.
不过严格地说  那不是我的管辖范围
Although, strictly speaking, that doesn't fall within my purview.
好了  好  我猜大家一定在想
All right then. Well, I imagine that you're all wondering
自己为什么会到这儿来
why you find yourselves here.
好在  邓布利多早有预料
And in anticipation of that,
并且让我来给在座的各位传个话
Dumbledore asked that I convey a message.
既然格林德沃拥有能预知
So, Grindelwald has the ability
并看见未来片段的能力
to see snatches of the future.
我们得假设他能在我们行动之前
So, we have to assume that he'll be able to anticipate
就知晓详细情况
what we do before we do it.
所以  如果我们想要打败他
So, if we hope to defeat him
来拯救我们的世界
and to save our world,
并且拯救你的世界  雅各布
to save your world, Jacob,
那么  我们最好的方法就是去迷惑他
then our best hope is to confuse him.
打断一下
'Scuse me.
对不起  要怎样迷惑一个  能预知未来的人
I'm sorry. How do you confuse a guy that can see the future?
用反视法
Countersight.
完全正确
Exactly.
最好的计划就是没有计划
The best plan being no plan.
又或者  许多个互相交错的计划
Or, many overlapping plans.
就这么迷惑他
Thus, confusion.
- 我已经糊涂了  - 事实上
- It's working on me right now.  - In fact,
邓布利多让我给你一件东西  雅各布
Dumbledore asked that I give you something, Jacob.
蛇木做的
It's snakewood.
所以  也算是稀有
It's, uh, somewhat rare.
你没跟我开玩笑吧
Are you kiddin' me right now?
- 这个是真的  - 是的
- Is this thing real?  - Yes.
不过它没有杖芯  所以说  算是吧
Well, it doesn't have a core, so sort of, but yes.
算是真家伙
It's sorta real?
更重要的是  我们去的地方你会用得上
More importantly, where we're going, you'll need it.
对了  忒修斯  我想这个是给你的
Now, there's something for you too, I think, Theseus.
泰迪  乖  快松手
Teddy, please let go now.
泰迪  快点儿松手
Teddy, please let go.
别这样  泰迪  听话好不好
No. Teddy, will you behave?
这个是给忒修斯的
This is Theseus'...
那是…
Um, that's...
对  没错
Well, of course.
现在一切都说得通了
Now everything makes sense.
拉莉  我想你已经收到阅读材料了
Um, Lally, I believe you were given some reading material?
有句俗话说
You know what they say.
书能载你游遍世界再回到原地
A book can take you around the world and back,
只需要打开书本就能做到
all you have to do is open it.
她说得对
She ain't kiddin'.
对了  还有邦缇  是给你的
Yes, uh, Bunty, um...
这个东西  他吩咐过我  只能给你一个人看
that's for you. I was told it was for your eyes only.
- 还有  卡玛  - 我已万事俱备
- And, Kama.  - I have what I need.
蒂娜呢  她…
What about Tina?
- 蒂娜会来吗  - 蒂娜抽不出时间
- Uh, is Tina coming?  - Tina's not available.
蒂娜她升职了  现在非常非常忙
Tina's been promoted, she's very, very busy from...
据我所知是这样
Well, from what I understand.
蒂娜现在担任  美国傲罗办公室的负责人
Tina's been made head of the American Auror Office.
我们两个很熟  她是一个很了不起的女人
We know each other well. She's quite a remarkable woman.
确实是
She is.
那么就是这支队伍
So, this is the team that's gonna take down
要去对抗一百年来  最危险的黑巫师吗
the most dangerous wizard we've faced in over a century.
一个神奇动物学家和他的得力助手
A magizoologist, his indispensable assistant,
一名教师
a schoolteacher,
一个出身于法国古老魔法世家的巫师
a wizard descended from a very old French family, and...
还有拿着假魔杖的
a Muggle baker
麻瓜烘焙师
with his fake wand.
我们还有你  伙计
Hey, we got you too, pal,
他有个真魔杖
and his wand works.
是
true
谁说我们没有胜算来着
Who wouldn't like our chances?
[德语] 女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen.
途经德累斯顿和布拉格 前往布拉迪斯拉发的…
Via Dresden and Prague to Bratislava...
…特快列车已抵达六号站台
...The express train has arrived at platform 6.
请立即上车
Please get on the bus immediately.
没事的  小家伙
You're all right, little one.
柏林
Berlin.
好极了
Wonderful.
卡玛
Kama,
注意安全
stay safe.
我现在也得走了  纽特
I must be going too now, Newt.
没有人可以知道一切
No one can know everything,
你也一样
not even you.
到了
Right.
对  就是这里
Well, here it is.
(安东·沃格尔)
- 我们要去德国魔法部吗  - 没错
- German Ministry of Magic?  - Yes.
我们来这里一定有原因吧
I take it we're here for a reason.
是的  我们现在得去参加一个茶会
Yes, we have a tea ceremony to attend,
而且如果不抓紧时间  就赶不上了
and if we don't hurry up, we'll be late.
雅各布  快跟上队伍
Jacob, stay with the group.
(格林德沃  因严重恶性犯罪并密谋 颠覆魔法世界而被通缉)
(巫师法力强大且极度危险 悬赏：5000)
桑托斯
Santos!
Santos! Santos! Santos!
桑托斯
刘洮
Liu Tao.
晚上好
Evening...
赫尔穆特
Helmut.
忒修斯
Theseus.
[德语] 他们哪儿来的
Where did they come from?
嘿  一起的
Hey, hey. They're with me.
桑托斯
Santos! Santos!
Santos!
(投维辛西亚·桑托斯一票)
桑托斯
Santos!
火焰熊熊
Incendio.
(最高领导 巴西国际巫师联合会)
(投维辛西亚·桑托斯一票)
- 我们应该不是来吃小三明治的  - 是的
- I take it we're not here for the finger sandwiches.  - Uh, no,
- 我是来这儿给人传话的  - 传什么话
- I have a message to deliver.  - A message?
给谁
To who?
沃格尔先生  很荣幸能见到你
Mr. Vogel, it's a pleasure to be here.
你好  不必客气
It's an honor to meet you.
你在开玩笑
You are joking.
没有
No.
我来这里做什么  我们出去吧
What am I even doing here? Let's go outside.
我不擅长应对这种场合
I'm not very good in these situations.
这种场合怎么了
These situations?
这么多人  还都是达官显贵
With all the people, the fancy people.
你好
Hello.
我看见你走进来
I saw you enter the room
当时心里就在想
and I thought to myself,
伊迪丝  那个人看上去真是有趣
Edith, that's an interesting-looking man.
雅各布·科瓦尔斯基
Jacob Kowalski.
你好吗  很高兴见到你
How are you? Very nice to meet you.
科瓦尔斯基先生  你从哪里来
And where is it you hail from, Mr. Kowalski?
皇后区
Queens.
嘿  沃格尔先生  打扰一下
Sorry, Herr Vogel. Sorry,
能跟您说句话吗
I wonder if I could have a word?
梅林胡子  你是斯卡曼德先生吧
Merlin's beard, it's Mr. Scamander, isn't it?
沃格尔先生
Herr Vogel...
没关系  不用过来  没事
It's okay. Don't come here. It's okay.
一位朋友托我给您带话
I have a message from a friend,
而且  情况十万火急
and it cannot wait.
去做正义之事
Do what is right,
而非容易之事
not what is easy.
他说这很重要  让我今晚务必找到你
He said it was important that I reach you tonight,
再把这句话亲口告诉你
that you hear them tonight, the words.
到时间了  先生
It's time, sir.
现在他在柏林吗
Is he here? In Berlin?
不  他当然不在
No, of course not.
世界一片火海  为什么要离开霍格沃茨呢
Why leave Hogwarts when the world outside is burning?
谢谢你  斯卡曼德先生
I thank you, Mr. Scamander.
非常感谢  谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
今晚在这里我看到了许多熟悉的面孔
I see many familiar faces here tonight.
同事们  朋友们
Colleagues, friends,
对手们
foes.
在接下来的四十八小时之内
Within the next 48 hours,
诸位将与魔法世界的同胞们
you, along with the rest of the Wizarding World,
一起选出我们的下一届领导者
will choose our next great leader.
我们眼下做出的选择
A choice that will shape our lives
将塑造子孙后代的生活
for generations to come.
我本人对此丝毫不怀疑
I have little doubt that,
无论是谁赢得本次选举
no matter who should triumph,
接任魔法联盟的都是一位有才之人
the Confederation will be in able hands.
无论是刘洮
Liu Tao.
或是维辛西亚·桑托斯
Vicencia Santos.
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
而且在这样的时刻  让我们牢记
It's in moments such as these we are reminded
正是这般权力的和平交接
that it is this peaceful transfer of power
代表着我们的人文精神
which marks our humanity
并向全魔法界表明
and demonstrates to the world that,
尽管我们之间存在分歧
despite our differences,
但是所有人都有发声的权利
all voices deserve to be heard...
即便是那种  很多人都不乐意听到的声音
even voices which many may find disagreeable.
纽特
Newt.
那些人里有没有眼熟的
Any of those lot look familiar to you?
在巴黎
Paris.
莉塔出事那晚
The night that Leta...
他们是格林德沃的人
They were with Grindelwald.
综上所述  在经过广泛细致的调查之后
And so, after an extensive investigation,
国际巫师联合会现已对案件
the Confederation has concluded
作出判决  同时也已认定
that insufficient evidence exists
起诉被告人盖勒特·格林德沃
to prosecute Gellert Grindelwald
对麻瓜社会所犯种种罪行一案  证据不足
for the crimes against the Muggle community
所以在此免除
of which he was accused.
他之前所有被指控的罪行
He is hereby absolved of all his alleged crimes.
开玩笑的吧  要给他脱罪
Are you kidding me? They're letting the guy off?
他杀人的时候我就在场
I was there, he was killing people.
你们被捕了
You're under arrest.
你们所有人
All of you.
放下魔杖
Wands down!
[德语] 把他带走
Take him away.
忒修斯
Theseus.
Theseus!
纽特  现在不行
Newt, Newt. Not here.
纽特  我们在这儿没有胜算
Newt, we don't stand a chance.
走吧
Let's go.
纽特  这儿已经被他们占领了
Newt, they have the German Ministry.
- 我们必须赶紧走  - 真的假的
- We've got to go.  - Whoa, whoa, whoa.
这样不对  根本就不是正义
It ain't right. That's not justice.
还广泛细致的调查  我就在场
"Extended investigation." I was there.
你在场  你在场吗  我就在场
Were you there? Were you there? I was there.
你们放走了凶手
You just let a killer off!
雅各布  得走了  赶快走
Jacob. We have to go. We have to go.
雅各布  我们快走
Jacob, let's go.
味道很不错
That's very good.
她最喜欢了
Her favorite.
以前她总问妈妈要  记得吗
Remember how she begged Mother to make it?
阿利安娜
Ariana.
母亲说这能让她平静下来
Mother claimed it calmed her,
- 可是我觉她是一厢情愿  - 阿不思
- but I think that was wishful thinking.  - Albus.
我也在
I was there.
我们在一个屋檐下长大
I grew up in the same house.
你看到的一切我都见过
Everything you saw, I saw.
所有东西
Everything.
看看门上的牌子  你这个蠢货
Read the sign, you stupid sod.
很抱歉来打扰你  阿不思
I'm sorry to disturb you, Albus.
说吧  怎么了
Tell me, what is it?
柏林出事了
It's Berlin.
怎么回事
What happened?
沃格尔  他已经赦免了  盖勒特的全部罪行
Vogel has absolved Gellert of all his crimes.
他自由了  说是证据不足
He's free. He says there's no proof.
在莉塔·莱斯特兰奇被杀当晚
He tried to arrest Aurors who were there
他还试图逮捕那些当时在场的傲罗
the night Leta Lestrange was murdered.
纽特  拉莉  还有那个麻瓜都没事
Newt, Lally, and the Muggle are all fine.
(你知道是怎样的感觉吗)
他们逃了出来
They managed to escape.
真是令人失望
Rather disappointing.
我得找人帮我代一下明天早上的课
I'm going to need someone to cover my morning classes.
- 能不能请你帮个忙  - 当然可以
- Can I impose on you?  - Of course.
- 阿不思  请一定…  - 好的  我  我尽量吧
- And, Albus, please be...  - I'll do my best.
晚上好  阿不福思
Evening, Aberforth.
晚上好  麦格
Evening, Minerva.
对不起  刚才我说你是个蠢货
Apologies for calling you a stupid sod.
我接受你这个道歉了
Apology accepted.
恐怕我今晚不能在这儿久留了
I'm afraid I'll have to cut our evening short.
要去拯救世界了  对吗
Off to save the world, are we?
那得找一个比我厉害的人
That will take a better man than me.
(你知道孤身一人 是怎样的感觉吗)
问都别问
Don't ask.
(你知道孤身一人 是怎样的感觉吗)
成千上万人都在街头高呼你的名字
There are thousands in the streets chanting your name.
你现在自由了
You're a free man.
去通知他们准备出发
Tell the others to prepare to leave.
- 今晚走  - 明天
- Tonight?  - Tomorrow.
明早有个人会过来
We'll have a visitor in the morning.
凤凰为什么总跟着他
Why does it stay with him?
一定是察觉到了他要做的事
It must sense what he's about to do.
你能确定…
And you're sure
他真杀得了邓布利多吗
that he can kill Dumbledore?
痛苦使他强大
His pain is his power.
我打听的那个人
The man that I am inquiring about
现在可是英国傲罗办公室的负责人
is the head of the British Auror Office.
你们怎么能把
How can you have misplaced
英国傲罗办公室的负责人给弄丢
the head of the British Auror Office?
刚才就已经说清楚了
As our contention said,
我们从来就没有抓过他
since he was never in our custody,
不可能把他弄丢
we never misplaced him.
先生  当晚有几十人在场
Sir, there were dozens of people there.
- 任何一个人都可以作证  - 你的名字是…
- Any one of them could corroborate...  - And your name is?
我们还是走吧
Let's get out of here.
等一下  就是那个人
Wait a minute, that's the guy.
对不…过来  你过来
Come here. Come here.
麻烦等一下  嘿
Excuse me! Hey!
就是那个人  他知道忒修斯在哪儿  你好
That's the guy. He knows where Theseus is. Hello!
忒修斯在哪里
Where's Theseus?
就是他  他知道忒修斯的事
That's him. He knows about Theseus.
纽特
Newt.
阿不思  我们…
Albus.
忒修斯是被带到厄克斯塔去了
Theseus has been taken to the Erkstag.
可那里不是好几年前就关闭了吗
Wait, no, but the Erkstag shut down years ago.
对  不过
Yes, well,
德国魔法部把那里  改造成一个秘密关押点
it's the Ministry's secret little bed and breakfast now.
拿着这个才能见到他
You'll need this to see him.
还有这个
And one of these.
和这个
And this.
等等
Wait, wait, wait.
看起来  新魔杖挺满意  科瓦尔斯基先生
I trust you're enjoying your wand, Mr. Kowalski?
我吗
Me?
谢谢你  邓布利多先生  那是个好东西
Oh, uh... Yeah, thank you, Mr. Dumbledore. It's a real pip.
建议你最好随身携带  希克斯教授
I advise you to keep it close. Professor Hicks.
邓布利多
Dumbledore.
如果说  你有空闲时间的话
Assuming you're not otherwise engaged,
不过即便你有安排
and frankly even if you are,
我还是建议你去参加  今晚的候选人晚宴
I encourage you to attend tonight's candidates' dinner.
带上科瓦尔斯基
Take Mr. Kowalski.
今晚一定会有人企图行刺
I'm quite certain there'll be an assassination attempt.
你要是能阻止那人的计划
Anything you can do to scotch that
我会十分感激的
will be greatly appreciated.
我义不容辞  乐意接受这个挑战
It's my pleasure. I shall welcome the challenge.
更何况  我还有雅各布帮忙
Besides, I'll have Jacob with me.
用不着担心
Oh, not to worry.
希克斯教授的防御魔法  可谓是炉火纯青
Professor Hicks' defensive magic is superb.
我们回头见
Until next time.
他真会说话  不过  他没说错  炉火纯青
Such a flatterer. Well, not really. It is superb.
阿不思  我想问一下
Albus! I was just wondering...
对了
Yes.
- 手提箱  - 对
- The case.  - Yes.
你就放心吧  它由可靠之人保管
Rest assured, it's in safe hands.
(奥托·爱德华皮革制品)
要帮忙吗
Can I help you?
是的
Yes.
麻烦你帮我仿制一下这只手提箱
I'd like to have this case replicated, please.
没问题
Certainly.
不  千万别打开它
Oh. No, you mustn't open it.
我是说  其实没有那个必要
Um, I mean, it's not necessary.
里面是什么样并不重要
The interior isn't important.
要仿制这个手提箱的确没什么问题
I see no reason I can't make you one.
快进去
Get in!
- 东西留这儿就行  - 哦  不行
- If you leave it here.  - Oh. No...
我不可以留下它
I couldn't leave it.
还有我需要不止一个仿制品
And I'll be needing more than one.
是这样
You see, um...
是我丈夫  他这个人粗心大意
My husband... he's a bit absentminded.
总是会忘东忘西
He's always forgetting things.
前几天他连跟我结了婚都忘了
Just the other day, he forgot he was married to me.
是不是很离谱
Can you imagine?
但我很爱他
But I love him.
那请问你到底是想做几个呢
Exactly how many were you thinking?
我需要六个
Half a dozen,
而且两天后我就得取货
and I'll need them in two days' time.
把手举起来
Show your hands.
你是谁
Who are you?
我叫尤瑟夫·卡玛
My name is Yusuf Kama.
- 来访的是哪位啊  - 你的仰慕者
- Who's our visitor?  - I'm an admirer.
你杀了他的妹妹
You murdered his sister.
她的名字叫莉塔
Her name was Leta.
莉塔·莱斯特兰奇
Leta Lestrange.
对
Ah, yes.
- 你们兄妹同属一支古老的血统  - 曾经是
- You and your sister share an ancient bloodline.  - Shared.
这是我们的唯一共同点
That's the only thing we shared.
邓布利多派你来的
Dumbledore sent you,
对不对
am I right?
他怕你已经得到了某只动物
He fears you're in possession of a creature.
也怕你将用它来做的事
He fears the use you may put it to.
是他派我来监视你的
He sent me here to spy on you.
你想让我告诉他些什么
What would you like me to tell him?
奎妮
Queenie.
他说的是真话吗
Is he telling the truth?
还有什么
What else?
他虽然信奉你的理念
Even though he believes in you,
但心中仍放不下你的杀妹之仇
he holds you responsible for his sister's death.
他时刻思念着逝去的妹妹
He carries her absence with him every day.
每一次呼吸都提醒着他  妹妹已经不在了
Every breath he takes is a reminder that she breathes no more.
那你应该不会介意
Then I presume you won't mind
我把你从痛苦的记忆里解放出来
if I relieve you of your sister's memory.
对吧
Right?
对
Right.
好了
There.
好多了
Better?
我想也是
I thought so.
当我们允许自己被愤怒所吞噬
When we allow ourselves to be consumed by anger,
那只是作茧自缚罢了
the only victim is ourself.
我们刚要做好准备出发呢
Now, we were just about to depart.
要不要和我们一起走
Perhaps you'd like to join us?
来吧
Come,
我们可以多聊聊  那位共同的朋友  邓布利多
we can talk some more about our mutual friend, Dumbledore.
你先请
After you.
(瓦尔彻旅行社)
你好  克雷登斯
Hello, Credence.
你知道举目无亲
Do you know what it's like
总是孤身一人
to have no one?
是怎样的感觉吗
To always be alone?
是你
It's you.
你就是在镜子上留言的那个人
You're the one sending messages in the mirror.
我姓邓布利多
I'm a Dumbledore.
你们却抛弃了我
You abandoned me.
你我的身上流淌着  来自同一家族的血脉
The same blood that runs my veins runs yours.
它不是为你而来的
He's not here for you.
是为了我
He's here for me.
事情真相往往并非如你所见  克雷登斯
Things are not quite what they appear, Credence,
不管别人告诉了你什么
no matter what you've been told.
我的名字是奥睿利乌斯
My name is Aurelius.
他欺骗了你  点燃了你的怒火
He's lied to you. Kindled your hate.
他告诉你的不是真相
What he's told you isn't true...
不过我们确实有血缘关系
but we do share the same blood.
你的确姓邓布利多
You are a Dumbledore.
我很抱歉你这么痛苦
I'm sorry for your pain.
我们之前真的不知情
We didn't know, I promise.
(禁止入内 不得擅闯)
(厄克斯塔)
我是来这儿看我哥哥的
I've come to see my brother.
他叫做忒修斯·斯卡曼德
His name is Theseus Scamander.
抱歉  那是…
Sorry, that's, uh...
魔杖
Wand.
那是…我是一名神奇动物学家
Oh, that's, uh... I'm... I'm a magizoologist.
它是完全无害的  这个小家伙就是个小宠物
He's perfectly harmless. He's... He's just a pet, really.
对不起
Sorry.
那是泰迪
That's Teddy.
老实说  它可不是个省油的灯
He's a total nightmare, truth be told.
它们得留在这里
They stay here.
我怎么才能知道他在哪儿呢
So, how will I know where to find him?
不是你哥哥吗
He's your brother?
- 是的  - 你按照他的长相去找不就成了
- Yes.  - He will be the one who looks like your brother.
我去去就回  皮克
I will be back, Pick.
说到做到
On my word.
我去去就回  皮克
"I'll be back, Pick."
说到做到
"On my word."
说不定我哪天还能当上魔法部部长呢
And I'll be Minister of Magic one day.
- 把车开到后门去  这里不安全  - 不用
- Take us 'round the back. It's not safe here.  - No.
- 摇下来  - 什么
- Roll it down.  - What?
车窗  把它摇下来
The window. Roll it down.
格林德沃
Grindelwald! Grindelwald!
不  不要
No. No!
那些人不是建议我们倾听他们的声音
Those people aren't suggesting we listen to them.
(格林德沃 投维辛西亚·桑托斯一票)
同样也不是提出请求
They aren't asking us to listen.
他们在强烈要求
They're demanding it.
你不会真的提议  允许那个人参与竞选吧
You're actually proposing that that man be allowed to stand?
是的
Yes.
就是要让他参选
Yes, let him stand.
格林德沃
Grindelwald
格林德沃想让麻瓜和巫师开战
Gellert Grindelwald wants a Muggle-wizard war,
倘若真的如他所愿
and if he gets his wish,
不仅会毁了麻瓜世界  还会毁了魔法世界
he won't just destroy their world, he'll destroy ours as well.
所以说  他不能获胜
Which is why he cannot win.
我们让他成为候选人  让大家来投票
Let him stand as a candidate. Let the people vote.
即便他落选了  那也是民众之愿
When he loses, the people will have spoken.
但是如果不给他们发声的权利
But deny them their voices,
那么大街小巷将会血流成河
and those streets will run with blood.
忒修斯
Theseus.
拉莉
Lally,
那个发型奇怪
the guy with the hair,
坐伊迪丝旁边的人
sitting next to Edith.
像是会杀人的样子
He looks like he can kill somebody.
他长得很像我叔叔多米尼克
He also looks like my Uncle Dominic.
那你的叔叔多米尼克  是挪威魔法部的部长吗
Is your Uncle Dominic the Norwegian Minister of Magic?
不是
No.
我猜也不是
Didn't think so.
奎妮
Queenie.
那好吧
桑托斯夫人  很荣幸
Madam Santos, a pleasure.
你的支持者们真是热情
Your supporters are in fine voice.
你的也是如此  格林德沃先生
As are yours, Mr. Grindelwald.
- 你是来救我的吗  - 是这么打算的
- Rescuing me, are you?  - That's the general idea.
那想必
And I presume this,
你之所以用这个姿势走路一定是
whatever it is that you are doing,
- 战略需要  - 没错  这是一种拟态仿生技巧
- is strategic.  - Yes, a technique called limbic mimicry.
理论上说  可以缓解动物的
It discourages violent engagement,
暴力倾向
theoretically.
其实  我以前只试用过一次而已
I've only actually ever attempted it once before.
效果怎么样
And the results?
还没有定论
Inconclusive.
因为那是在实验室里  严控条件下模拟的环境
Course that was a laboratory setting and the conditions were strictly controlled, and the...
而且  目前的情况更加不稳定
Well, the current conditions are more volatile,
所以更难判断最终结果会是怎样
so making it less predictive of the ultimate outcome.
这次的最终结果应该是…
The ultimate outcome presumably...
我们
We!
可以活着出去吧
being our survival.
干得好  走吧
Well done, come on.
- 所以下面的计划是  - 你拿着
- And the plan is?  - Hold this.
你那样做能有什么用
What the bloody hell was that for?
我们需要帮助
We're gonna need some help.
对
yes.
跟着我
Follow me.
跟上
Come on.
你这样扭得不对
You're not swiveling properly.
这么扭  扭起来  也要小心翼翼的
Swivel... Swivel, but delicately.
我跟你扭得一模一样  纽特
I'm swiveling like you're swiveling, Newt.
我看着可差远了
I don't believe you are.
接着扭
Swivel.
去找他
Go to him.
奎妮
Queenie.
跟他说没关系
Tell him it's all right.
看得出来他失败了
I can see he's failed.
他还会有机会的
He'll have another chance.
我最看重的是他的忠心
It's his loyalty I most value.
在这儿别动
Stay here.
不好意思
Apologies.
天哪
Oh, boy.
放过她
Let her go.
你说什么
Excuse me?
有刺客
Assassin!
救命啊
Help!
等等
No, wait.
纽特
Newt!
速速飞来  抓住领带
Accio! Grab the tie.
那是个门钥匙
That was a Portkey.
对
Yeah.
多亏你们两个
Well done, you two.
虽然你们两个都没问我
Not that either of you asked,
不过我建议你们一定要把魔咒课学好
but I would highly recommend learning Charms.
拉莉
Lally.
你俩怎么才来
What kept you two?
我们遇到了一些麻烦  你们呢
Uh, we encountered some complications. You?
我们也遇到了一些麻烦
We encountered some complications.
(预言家日报：凶残的麻瓜)
雅各布想刺杀格林德沃
Jacob tried to murder Grindelwald?
这事说来话长
It's a long story.
真的是蛇木做的吗
Is it really snakewood?
那还有假  当然是蛇木
Yes, it's really snakewood.
能不能…
Can I...
很危险的
Very dangerous.
魔力太强了
It's very powerful.
很罕见  如果落到坏人手里
It's rare. If it got in the wrong hands, you know,
就不妙了
mess you up.
那你是从哪儿得来的
Where did you get it?
圣诞节礼物
I got it for Christmas.
雅各布  看看是谁来了
Jacob, look who I found.
是我的巫师朋友们  纽特和忒修斯
It's my wizard friends, Newt and Theseus.
我们就像这样  懂吗  这个才是我
We're like this, okay, and that's me right there.
我得走了  好了  你们玩
I gotta go. All right, have fun.
别做不该做的事
Don't do anything I wouldn't do.
这也太不可思议了吧
Can you believe this place?
这么多迷你的小女巫和小巫师满地跑
They got pint-sized little witches and wizards running around here.
可不是嘛
You don't say.
那刺客就是我
I was the assassin.
纽特和忒修斯都在霍格沃茨上过学
Newt and Theseus both went to Hogwarts.
这我知道  这儿的学生都很热情
Oh, I knew that. Well, they're being very nice to me.
这是那几个斯莱特林小男生给我的
The Slytherin boys over there, they gave me these.
很好吃  有人要吗
They're delicious. Who wants one?
我本人向来都欣赏不来  蟑螂团子的味道
I never cared for cockroach clusters much myself,
不过  蜂蜜公爵的应该是最好的
although Honeydukes are supposed to be the best.
不要吃那个了
Don't eat that.
先走吧
Off you go.
麦格
McGonagall.
阿不思
Albus.
太棒了  你们都做得非常好
Well done. All of you, well done.
恭喜大家
Congratulations.
- 恭喜我们  - 没错
- Congratulations?  - Indeed.
希克斯教授成功阻止了一场暗杀行动
Professor Hicks managed to foil an assassination.
而你还活着  而且精神不错
And you are alive and you are well.
一切都没按计划走
The fact that everything
但是我们的计划就是不按计划走
didn't go precisely to plan was precisely the plan.
反视法的基本招式
Countersight 101.
阿不思  恕我直言  这不是又回到原点了吗
Albus, forgive me, but aren't we back where we started?
要我说  我们现在处境
Actually, I would argue that things are...
比开始还要差很多
a great deal worse.
你还没告诉他们吧
You haven't told them, have you?
他们已经允许格林德沃参加竞选了
Grindelwald's been allowed to stand in the election.
- 什么  - 怎么会
- What?  - But how?
因为沃格尔选择了容易
Because Vogel chose easy
而非正义
over right.
没事的
It's all right.
不丹
Bhutan.
答对了  赫奇帕奇加三分
Correct. Three points to Hufflepuff.
不丹王国
The kingdom of Bhutan
位于东喜马拉雅山脉的高处
sits high in the Eastern Himalayas.
那是一个美得无与伦比的国度
It's a place of indescribable beauty.
我们研习的一些很重要的魔法  都源自于那里
Some of our most important magic has its origins there.
据说只要你用心聆听
They say if you listen carefully enough,
就能听到往昔的密语
the past whispers to you.
这里也是选举进行的会场
It also happens to be where the election will be held.
他赢不了的吧
He can't win, can he?
就在几天前  他的身份还是一名逃犯
Only a few days ago he was a fugitive from justice.
现在却摇身一变成了
Now he is an official candidate
国际魔法联盟主席的候选人
in the International Confederation of Wizards.
危险的时代  偏爱危险的人才
Dangerous times favor dangerous men.
顺便提一句
By the way,
我们晚上去村子里和我弟弟吃饭
we'll be dining with my brother in the village.
这之前若还需要什么  找米勒娃就行
Should you need anything before then, Minerva is here.
邓布利多还有弟弟
Dumbledore has a brother?
我们到了
Here we are.
- 邦缇  你也在啊  - 是的
- Bunty, you're here.  - Yes.
- 它怎么样  - 一切都好
- How is she?  - Oh, she's fine.
阿尔菲又干什么了
What's Alfie done now?
你最近没有再去咬蒂莫西的屁股吧
Wait, you've not been biting. Timothy's bottom again, have you?
布罗德克女士
Miss Broadacre,
我弟弟招待得应该还算周到吧
I trust my brother has been a gracious host?
是的  特别热情周到
Yes, ever so gracious.
很高兴你这么说
I'm delighted to hear.
对了  已经给诸位  在村子里安排好了住处
Uh, so, rooms have been arranged for you in the village,
我弟弟阿不福思
and Aberforth here
会给大家准备美味的晚餐  他自创的食谱
will prepare you a delicious dinner, his own recipe.
不够的话  这边还有
There's more of that if you want it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢
Thanks.
不可思议
Astonishing.
从没吃过看着这么恶心  却这么好吃的东西
Never has something that looks so repellent tasted so delicious.
这个小家伙是谁  安静点儿好吗
Who is this little one? Do you mind?
它是只麒麟  雅各布
She's a Qilin, Jacob.
十分罕见的物种
She's incredibly rare.
魔法世界最受喜爱的神奇动物之一
One of the most beloved creatures in the Wizarding World.
为什么
Why?
因为它能看透你的灵魂
'Cause she can see into your soul.
开玩笑的吧
You're kidding me.
不  倘若你为人善良
No. So, if you are good
而且值得信赖  它能看到
and worthy, then she'll see that.
与此同时  如果你残酷
But if, on the other hand, you're cruel
而且虚伪狡诈  它也能看出来
and deceitful, then she'll know that too.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
它是直接告诉你还是…
Does she just tell you that or...
它不会用嘴说  它用鞠躬表达
Not exactly tells. Well, she bows,
它只会在真正内心纯良的人面前鞠躬
but only in the presence of someone truly pure of heart.
当然  大多数人都达不到标准
I mean, almost none of us are, of course,
无论我们有多一心向善
no matter how good of a person one tries to be.
许多许多年以前  曾经有一段时间
There was actually a time, many, many years ago,
是由麒麟为我们选领导者的
when the Qilin chose who'd lead us.
不行
No...
好了  好了好了
Okay. All right, already.
来吃吧
Here you go.
真活泼
Thriving.
- 它是饿了  - 看看它
- He's just hungry.  - Look at him.
- 它很喜欢你  雅各布  - 好吧
- She really likes you, Jacob.  - Oh, all right.
没关系
It's okay.
(我想回家)
好  这就对了
Okay, that's right.
跟我去吧
Come with me.
我会帮你的
I'll help you.
他是你的儿子  阿不福思
He's your son, Aberforth.
他需要你
He needs you.
纽特
Newt.
进来吧
Come in.
阿不思  楼下的镜子上出现了一行字
Albus, the mirror downstairs, there's a message.
把门关上
Close the door.
那是克雷登斯写的  纽特
It's from Credence, Newt.
我弟弟爱上了一个姑娘
my brother fell in love as well,
戈德里克山谷人
with a girl from the Hollow.
她最终被驱逐
She was sent away.
那时就有传言说她生了孩子
There were rumors about a child.
- 克雷登斯…  - 他姓邓布利多
- Credence...  - He's a Dumbledore.
倘若我待他好一点
If I'd been a better friend...
或者做一个更加称职的哥哥
to Aberforth, if I'd been a better brother...
他也许就会对我倾诉
he might have confided in me.
情况也许就会不同  而那个孩子
Perhaps things would have been different, and this boy...
就可能留下来  成为我们的家人
could have been part of our lives, part of our family.
克雷登斯没救了  我想你也知道这一点
Credence can't be saved, I know you know that.
但他或许还可以拯救我们
But he may yet be able to save us.
凤凰灰烬
Phoenix ash.
那只鸟在他身边  是因为他要死了
The bird comes to him because he's dying,
纽特
Newt.
我了解这些迹象
I know the signs.
要知道
You see...
我妹妹也是一个默然者
my sister was an Obscurial.
和克雷登斯一样  她也没学会控制魔法
And like Credence, she never learned to express her magic.
后来那股力量黑化并开始毒害她
Over time it grew darker and began to poison her.
最痛心的是我们都无法缓解她的痛苦
Worst of all, none of us were capable of easing her pain.
能告诉我  她是怎么…
Can you tell me how it is that...
她是怎么离去的吗
or how it came to an end for her?
盖勒特和我计划好了要一起离开
Gellert and I had made plans to go away together.
我弟弟他不同意
My brother didn't approve.
一天晚上  他来找我们
One night, he confronted us.
我们大吵起来  互不相让
Voices were raised, threats made.
阿不福思愚蠢地拔出了他的魔杖
Aberforth drew his wand, which was foolish.
更加愚蠢的是  我也抽出了魔杖
I drew my wand, which was even more foolish.
盖勒特大笑着
Gellert just laughed.
没有人听到阿利安娜下了楼
No one heard Ariana coming down the stairs.
我也不确定是不是我的…
Can't say for certain it was my...
咒语
spell.
已经无所谓了
Doesn't really matter.
她前一秒还在那儿  后一秒就不在了
One minute she was there, and the next she was gone.
我很抱歉  阿不思
I'm so sorry, Albus.
但从另一个角度来说  或许这样
But if it's of any comfort, perhaps
省去了她许多痛苦
she was saved some pain...
够了  不要让我失望  纽特
Don't. Don't disappoint me, Newt.
尤其是你
You of all people.
你的诚恳是一份礼赠
Your honesty is a gift...
即便有时它会让人痛苦
even if at times a painful one.
楼下的朋友们一定很累了
Our friends downstairs will be tired
都想早些休息  你也…
and wanting to go home. You should...
你也去吧
You should go.
阿不思  拉莉曾经说过一段话  她说
Albus, Lally said something earlier
大多数人最终都是不完美的
about most of us being ultimately imperfect.
但即使我们犯了错  无论多大的错
But even if we make mistakes, terrible things...
我们还是可以尝试纠正
we can try to make things right.
这才是最重要的
And that's what matters...
尝试
trying.
我们支持你
We're with you.
谢谢
Thank you.
属于我们的时刻就快到了  兄弟姐妹们
Our time is close, my brothers and sisters.
不必再躲躲藏藏
Days of hiding are over.
这世界  将听到我们的呼声
The world will hear our voice.
震耳欲聋的呼声
And it will be deafening.
格林德沃
Grindelwald
你不是为了背叛邓布利多而来
You didn't come here to betray Dumbledore.
你心中
You know in
流淌着纯正巫师血脉
your pure-blood heart,
你属于这里
your place is here.
信任我就等于信任你自己
To believe in me is to believe in yourself.
证明你的忠心  卡玛先生
Prove your loyalty, Mr. Kama.
快快复苏  速速愈合
...Vulnera Sanentur.
Rennervate Vulnera Sanentur.
快快复苏  速速愈合
好了
There.
好了好了
There, there.
乖
There.
过来  看
Come, look.
这就是我们的特别之处
This is why we are special.
有意隐藏魔力
To conceal our powers
不仅仅是对我们自己身份的极大侮辱
is not merely an affront to ourselves...
更是罪
it's sinful.
还有另一只吗
Was there another?
另一只
Another?
那天晚上还有没有另外一只麒麟
That night, was there another Qilin?
应该没有
I don't think so...
你让我失望两次了
That's twice you failed me.
你不明白这对我是多大的威胁吗
Do you not understand the danger you put me in?
最后一次机会
One last chance.
明白了吗
Understood?
快去找
Find it.
嘿  纽特
Hey, Newt.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
这是有求必应屋
The room we require.
邦缇之前发给你们的票  大家都带好了吧
I trust you all have the tickets that Bunty gave you?
没有票的话是进不去选举会场的
You'll need them to gain access to the ceremony.
怎么样  纽特  看出哪个是你的了吗
What do you think, Newt? Can you tell which one is yours?
没有
No.
那就好  否则我该担心了
Good. I'd be worried if you could.
- 麒麟就在其中一个手提箱里吧  - 没错
- I assume the Qilin's in one of these cases.  - Yes.
- 是在哪个里呢  - 是啊  哪个呢
- Well, which one is it?  - Which one indeed.
跟三卡蒙特游戏一样
Ooh, it's like a three-card monte thing.
就是猜东西的游戏
Like a shell game thing.
就是  骗人的把戏
Like a short con.
不重要  是麻瓜玩的
Never mind, it's a Muggle thing.
格林德沃一定会倾尽自己的全力
Grindelwald will do anything within his powers
来抢我们手里这个
to get his hands on
珍稀的小家伙
our rare friend.
因此  此行的重中之重是
Therefore, it's essential that we keep
让他派出来的所有人都猜不到
whoever he dispatches on his behalf guessing,
好让麒麟安全地进入到选举会场
so the Qilin gets to the ceremony safely.
如果下午茶时间
If, by teatime,
麒麟  更不用说
the Qilin, not to mention
我们大家都还活着的话
all of us, are still alive,
那我们的行动就算是成功了
we should consider our efforts a success.
顺便说一句  玩三卡蒙特就从来没死过人
For the record, nobody ever died playing three-card monte.
这个区别很重要
An important distinction.
好了  一人拿一个手提箱  我们上路
All right, everybody choose a case and we'll be on our way.
科瓦尔斯基先生
Mr. Kowalski,
我们两个人一起先走一步
you and I will proceed together first.
我
Me?
好吧
Okay.
我十分期待你给我仔细讲讲
I'm looking forward to you educating me a little further
三卡蒙特游戏具体是怎么个玩法
on the finer points of three-card monte.
乐意至极
My pleasure.
那么
Well...
祝大家都有好运
Good luck, everybody.
大家好运
Good luck.
也祝你好运  邦缇姑娘
And you too, Bunty girl.
回见  邦缇
See you, Bunty.
我们作为领导层并没有忘记
It is not lost on those of us in leadership
眼下我们正处于一个四分五裂的世界
that we are currently a world divided.
每天都会有人谈起新的阴谋论
Each day brings talk of another conspiracy.
每小时都会有负面的谣传
Each hour another dark whisper.
而近几天随着我们  第三位候选人的出现
These whispers have only increased in recent days,
这些谣传已然愈演愈烈
with the addition of a third candidate.
要消除这些疑虑  让结果服众
There is only one way to leave absolutely no doubt
唯一的方法就是
that a worthy candidate exists
证明诸位眼前  这三个候选人中有真正的
amongst the three you have
贤能之人
been presented.
难道他有麒麟
Does he have kylin?
就算学校里的孩子
As every schoolboy
都十分清楚  麒麟
and girl knows, the Qilin
乃是这神奇的魔法世界中
is the purest of creatures
至纯至净的生物
in our wonderful magical world.
没有人可以骗过它
It cannot be deceived.
让麒麟带我们团结一心吧
Let the Qilin unite us.
(隐形兽)
桑托斯
Santos! Santos! Santos! Santos! Santos! Santos!
(投维辛西亚·桑托斯一票)
来
Come.
接下来去哪儿
Where to, next?
咱们要在这里暂别了
Uh, this is where I leave you.
等  等一下  你说什么  暂别
I'm... I'm sorry, you're what? Leaving me?
我得去见另一个人  科瓦尔斯基先生
I have to meet someone else, Mr. Kowalski.
不用担心
Not to worry,
你不会有事的
you'll be perfectly safe.
麒麟不在你这里
You don't have the Qilin.
一旦发现情况不妙  你可以扔了箱子就跑
Feel free to drop the case at the first hint of trouble.
还有件事  说了你不要介意
One other thing, if you don't mind me saying.
不要再怀疑自己了
You should stop doubting yourself.
你拥有的东西很多人一生都不曾拥有
You have something most men go their entire lives without.
知道是什么吗
Do you know what that is?
一颗充实的心
A heart that is full.
只有真正勇敢的人
Only a truly brave man
才能诚挚而毫不设防地
could open himself up so honestly
像你这样
and completely,
敞开心扉
as you do.
桑托斯
Santos! Santos! Santos!
手提箱  交出来
Cases, please.
嘿  伙计们
Hey, fellas.
他生气了
He's angry.
等等  先打开确认在不在
Wait. Open them, make sure it's in there.
蠢货
Idiots.
放开我
Let go of me
救我
Help me
放开我
Let go of me
他还能撑多久
How long does he have?
这里  你很危险  知道吗
Here. Hey. Hi. You're in danger, all right?
- 你得快走  - 那…
- You need to leave.  - Well...
我不能  我不能走  懂吗
I can't... I can't go, okay?
我不能回家
I can't come home.
对我来说太晚了
It's too late for me, all right?
我犯的一些错误  大得无法弥补
Some mistakes, they're just too big.
听我说好吗
Can you listen to me?
没时间了  有人跟踪我
There's no time. I was followed.
我甩掉了他们  但他们很快就会找到我
I gave 'em the slip, but it won't be long before they find me.
- 他们会发现的  - 我不在乎
- They're gonna find us.  - I don't care.
你是我的一切
All I got is us.
没有你我的人生毫无意义
I make no sense without us.
雅各布  什么  拜托
Jacob, what? Come on...
我已经不爱你了  你快走吧
I don't love you anymore. Just get outta here.
你最不会撒谎了  奎妮·戈德斯坦恩
You're the worst liar in the world, Queenie Goldstein.
- 听到了吗  - 什么
- You hear that? What?  - No.
那是个预兆  太好了
That's a sign. Oh, man.
- 拜托  - 来  过来
- Oh, come on.  - Come here, come here.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
拜托  闭上眼睛
Please close your eyes.
知道邓布利多说什么吗
You know what Dumbledore said to me?
不
No.
他说我有一颗充实的心
He said that I got a full heart.
他错了
He's wrong.
我的心永远都会给你留出位置
I'm always gonna have room in there for you.
- 是吗  - 是  你知道
- Yeah?  - Yeah. You know it.
看着我
Look at me.
奎妮·戈德斯坦恩
Queenie Goldstein.
(投维辛西亚·桑托斯一票)
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander.
我们还没有正式打过照面
We've never been properly introduced.
我叫亨丽埃塔·费歇尔
Henrietta Fischer,
沃格尔先生的随员
Herr Vogel's attache.
好的  你好
Yes, uh, hello.
我可以带你上去
I can take you up.
高级委员会的成员有一个独立入口
There's a private entrance for members of the High Council.
你只需要跟我走
If you just follow me.
不好意思  你为什么这么做
I'm sorry, why would you do that?
带我上去
Take me up?
难道还不明显吗
Isn't it obvious?
不  坦白说  不明显
No, frankly, it's, uh, not.
邓布利多派我来的
Dumbledore sent me.
我知道你手提箱里有什么  斯卡曼德先生
I know what you have in that case, Mr. Scamander.
(投维辛西亚·桑托斯一票)
他应该很快就到了
He should be here any minute.
怎么才来
What kept you?
感谢几位候选人的精彩讲话
I thank the candidates for their words.
每一位
Each
所发表的精彩演讲
represents a distinct vision
都代表了自己对于  如何塑造我们的魔法世界
of how we will not shape only our world,
以及非魔法世界的看法
but the non-magical world as well.
而接下来
Which brings us
就是本次仪式中最重要的一个环节
to the most important part of our ceremony,
麒麟的选择
the walk of the Qilin.
麒麟作出了选择
The Qilin has seen.
它看到了纯善和力量
Seen goodness, strength,
这都是指引我们前进的领导者
qualities essential to lead
必不可缺的品质
and to guide us.
诸位的选择呢
Who do you see?
格林德沃
Grindelwald
盖勒特·格林德沃  是我们魔法世界的新领袖
Gellert Grindelwald is the new leader of the magical world
口头表决通过
by acclamation.
就是这个人曾经试图刺杀我
This is the man who tried to take my life.
这个人
This man,
他没有一点儿魔法
who has no magic,
却想娶一个女巫  污染我们的血脉
who would marry a witch and pollute our blood,
这禁忌的结合只会令我们不堪
create a forbidden union that would make us less,
让我们像他的同类般弱小
make us weak, like his kind.
他可不是孤例  朋友们
He's not alone, my friends.
想像他这样做的人成千上万
There are thousands who seek to do the same.
这样的寄生虫只配得到一种对待
There can only be one response to such vermin.
不
No.
钻心剜骨
Crucio.
不
No!
快让他住手
Make him stop!
我们与麻瓜的战争
Our war with the Muggles
从今天打响
begins today.
格林德沃
Grindelwald
雅各布
Jacob.
他骗了你们
He's lying to you.
那个东西已经死了
That creature is dead.
等一下  等等
Not now. Wait.
他是为了骗你们
He did it to trick you.
他杀了麒麟  然后给它施咒
He killed it and bewitched it
好让大家觉得他有资格成为领袖
so that you might think him worthy to lead.
可他并不想领导你们
But he doesn't want to lead you.
他只想你们服从
He just wants you to follow.
谎言
Words.
这是精心编造的谎言
Words designed to deceive.
让各位怀疑亲眼所见的事实
To make you doubt what you've seen with your own two eyes.
那一夜有两只麒麟诞生
There were two Qilins born that night.
双胞胎  我知道的
A twin. And I know that...
- 我知道  - 证据呢
- I know that...  - Because?
你根本就没有证据
Because you have no proof.
因为并没有第二只麒麟
Because there was no second Qilin.
我说得对吗
Am I not right?
它的母亲被害  它…
Its mother had been killed, it...
那它在哪里  斯卡曼德先生
Then where is it now, Mr. Scamander?
没人可以知道一切  纽特
No one can know everything, Newt.
记得吗
Remember?
你好
Hello!
我不理解  真是
I don't get it.
它听不到的  小家伙
She can't hear you, little one.
它不在这儿
Not here...
或许在别处听着你的呼唤
but perhaps somewhere she's listening.
这才是真正的麒麟
This is the true Qilin.
好好看看
Look at it,
大家都可以亲眼看出来  这只才是真的
you can see it with your own eyes. This is the true...
刚才这个结果不能算数
This can't be allowed to stand.
必须重新进行投票
The vote must be taken again.
好了安东  履行职责
Come on, Anton. Do something.
你…
You...
不  别别别  拜托了
No, no, no, please.
我很荣幸
I'm honored.
但正如那天晚上你们两个一起出生
But just as two of you were born that night,
这里还有一个人
there's another here,
同样值得认可
equally worthy.
这一点我确定
I'm certain of it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不可能
It's impossible
还有谁会爱你  邓布利多
Who will love you now, Dumbledore?
你孤身一人了
You're all alone.
桑托斯
Santos!
我从不是你们的敌人
I was never your enemy.
从前
Then,
或现在
or now.
你有想念过我吗
Did you ever think of me?
一直想
Always.
回家吧
Come home.
它来了
Here she is.
你太棒了  邦缇
Well done, Bunty.
来吧  小家伙
Come on, little one.
对不起  我一定吓坏你了吧
I'm sorry. I must have given you an awful fright.
不  我觉得有时候
No, I think, um,
只有失去过才能更好地  体会到它的重要性
sometimes it takes losing something to realize quite how much it means.
(皇家辰星汽轮公司 纽约)
可有时候你本来就…
And sometimes you just...
有时候你本来就清楚
Sometimes you just know.
好了  进去吧
Right, in you pop.
科瓦尔斯基先生
Mr. Kowalski.
我欠你一个道歉
I owe you an apology.
我让你承受钻心咒的痛苦折磨
It... It was never my intent
绝对不是我的本意
for you to suffer the Cruciatus curse.
好
Yeah...
不过奎妮回来了  就算扯平了吧
Well, you know, we got Queenie back, so we're square.
我能问你个事吗
Hey, can I ask you a question?
这个我能留着吗  就算是留个纪念
Can I keep this? For, like, old times' sake?
我想不到还能有谁
I can't think
比你更配拥有它
of anyone more deserving.
谢谢你  教授
Thanks, Professor.
不可思议
Remarkable.
我不懂  你们不是不能互相攻击吗
But how? I thought you couldn't move against one another.
我们没有
We didn't.
他寻求杀戮  而我寻求护佑
He sought to kill, I sought to protect.
我们的魔咒遭遇了
Our spells met.
就当是天意吧
Let's call it fate.
不然的话  怎么才能实现我们的命运呢
After all, how else will we fulfill our destinies?
阿不思
Albus.
请答应我
Promise me.
务必找到他  阻止他
You'll find him and you'll stop him.
阿尔伯特  别忘了那些馅饼
Albert, don't forget the pierogis.
是  科瓦先生
Yes, Mr. K.
阿尔伯特
Albert.
果酱饼干最多烤八分钟
No more than eight minutes on the kolaczkis.
是  科瓦先生
Yes, Mr. K.
这孩子挺好
He's a sweet kid.
就是分不清蘑菇肉卷和白菜肉卷
He doesn't know the difference between paszteciki and golabki.
- 亲爱的  - 哇哦
- Hey, sweetheart.  - What?
纽特听不懂你说的话
Newt doesn't know what you're talking about.
我也听不懂你说的话
I don't know what you're talking about.
而你今天不需要管工作  还记得吗
And you are not working today, remember?
你没事吧  亲爱的
Oh, are you all right, honey?
是在为了祝词的事紧张  别紧张
Oh, you're nervous about the speech. Don't be nervous.
告诉他  亲爱的
Tell him, honey.
- 祝词的事不用紧张  - 我  我不紧张
- Don't be nervous about the speech.  - I'm not nervous.
这什么味
What is the smell?
怎么有一股糊味  阿尔伯特
Why is there burning? Albert?
我看你是在为别的事紧张吧
Mm. Maybe we're nervous about something else, huh?
我不知道你在说什么
I can't imagine what you're talking about.
(科瓦尔斯基烘焙坊  科瓦尔斯基品质烘焙)
第一次见到雅各布那天
So, the day that I first met Jacob...
The day that I first met Jacob,
我们都坐在斯蒂恩国家银行
we were both sitting in the Steen National Bank.
我万万没…
Never would I...
我猜你是伴娘吧
The maid of honor, I presume?
我猜你是伴郎吧
The best man, I gather?
- 你的发型不一样了  - 没有
- You've done something to your hair.  - No.
对  确实变了  就为…
No. Well, yes, actually, just...
- 就为今晚  - 很适合你
- Just for tonight.  - Well, it suits you.
谢谢你  纽特
Thank you, Newt.
- 你们好  - 嗨
- Hello.  - Hi.
看这是…
Look who's...
见到你太高兴了
So good to see you.
- 嗨  - 你还好吗
- Hi.  - How are you?
你这身真漂亮  拉莉
You look wonderful, Lally.
谢谢你  纽特  谢谢夸奖
Well, thank you, Newt. I appreciate it.
祝你好运
Good luck.
蒂娜  来
Tina, come on.
- 你跟我说说美国魔法部最近如何  - 里面见
- You must tell me how MACUSA's been.  - See you inside.
我呢  我这身怎么样
What about me? How do I look?
- 你没事吧  - 你也挺好
- You all right?  - You look fine.
- 确定没事  - 我没事
- You okay?  - Yeah, I'm all right.
不紧张吧
You're not nervous, are you?
刚拯救了世界  演讲可不能怯场
Can't be nervous about a speech after saving the world.
历史性的一天啊
It's a historic day.
从今天开始往后的日子
Where once was before,
和以前完全不一样了
there will now be after.
有趣的是
Funny
身在其中的我们却感觉它如此平淡
how historic days seem so ordinary when you're living them.
或许恢复正轨的世界本应如此吧
Well, perhaps that's what happens when the world gets things right.
偶尔平淡的日子真是让人高兴
Mm, it's jolly nice to know it happens occasionally.
我之前不知道你会不会来
I didn't know if I'd see you here.
我自己都不知道
I wasn't sure you would, either.
- 嘿  纽特  - 怎么了
- Hey, Newt.  - Yes.
雅各布说他好像把戒指弄丢了
Jacob seems to think he's lost the ring.
- 是在你那里吧  - 没丢  好着呢  在
- Please tell me you've got it.  - No, it's all good. Yep.
吓我一跳  哦  好的
That scared me. Jacob!
皮克真乖
Good man, Pick.
我可能应该…
I should probably, um...
谢谢你  纽特
Thank you, Newt.
- 谢什么  - 谢谢你的牺牲
- What for?  - Pick your poison.
没有你  我做不到这一切
I really couldn't have done it without you.
我随时愿意再次帮你
I'd do it again, by the way.
只要你开口
Should you ask.
好吧
Okay.
- 邦缇  - 邦缇
- Bunty!  - Bunty!
你们好
How do you do.
邦缇
Bunty!
你太漂亮了
Wow, you're so beautiful.
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
对  女朋友  你们真是…
Yes, girlfriends, you are...
这位是  这位是阿尔伯特
This is, um... This is Albert.
我不知道你们打过招呼了没有
I don't know if you've met Albert, yet?
我们打过招呼了
We said hello
- 拉莉你认识了  - 你好
- Have you met Lally?  - Hello!
《神奇动物3：邓布利多之谜》